

### DANIEL VALENTIN

**UX** Designer

Copenhagen

+45 22719298

#### O DETAILS O

#### Contact and address

Tjørnerækken 6, 2300 København +45 22719298

daniel.valentin.laursen@gmail.com dani763f.github.io/website/

#### Age and nationality

28 years old Danish

#### Other

Drivers license

### • QUALIFICATIONS •

User-oriented design

Data visualization

Specialization in UX Design + methodology

Adobe Suite

Microsoft Office

Figma

Blender

Linux

Docker & Virtualization

IT process understanding (LEAN, Six Sigma, Agile, ITIL, Scrum etc.)

#### LANGUAGE

Danish (First language) English

### • FREE TIME •

Open-Source software & Linux Selfhosting Computer Hardware Gaming Family



### ABOUT ME

My strength and passion is to understand, optimize and design IT solutions and processes. Whether the task is to implement, support or design new prototypes and solutions, for the last 5+ years I have worked professionally with the branches of IT in connection with my education from the IT University of Copenhagen. In my freetime i dabble with selfhosting, Linux and all things open-source.

### EXPERIENCE

# UX Consultant, Racing Kids · Freelance 2022 -

 Consulting and preparation of a new workflow for product import as well as general process optimization primarily in shopify.

# UX/IT Consultant, Hjorths Badehotel · Freelance 2018 - 2022

· IT support and process optimization tasks as well as maintenance and content for websites in wordpress.

### IT Support Specialist at ITSS Group Technology, Nordea 2016 - 2019

- · Incident and knowledge management tasks in various ERP systems.
- · Onboarding of new team members
- Close collaboration with other IT departments in Denmark, Finland, Norway, Sweden, India and many other countries.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Maintain a high service level and meet SLA targets for the department.

## Brand Ambassador, Gorm Larsen Nordic 2015 - 2016

- Sale and presentation of various hardware, including computers, printers, VR Headsets, smart phones and more.
- · Bookkeeping of sales and interactions in Gorm Larsen's in-house CRM system.
- · Installation and responsibility for exhibition stands and other logistics in connection with conferences.

# Webmaster, Restaurant Rusk · Freelance 2014 - 2018

Store employee, Creative Space APS 2014 - 2015

### EDUCATION

# $\ensuremath{\mathsf{MSc}}\xspace$ . Digital Design and Interactive technologies, IT University of Copenhagen 2021

The master's program provides a broad understanding of digital design processes from the initial studies of the design domain to testing and implementation. In-depth knowledge of data visualization, context and user analysis is provided, as well as a foundation for understanding of the role digital designs and services play in our society and culture today and in the future.

# $\mathsf{BSc} \cdot \mathsf{Global}$ Business Informatics, IT University of Copenhagen 2018

Global Business Informatics is an interdisciplinary study where you learn to see the possibilities of digital technologies and how they are used in organizational and societal settings. With a bachelor's degree in Global Business Informatics, you are able to work with sustainable development in private companies, public institutions and NGOs.

Student, Ørestad Gymnasium 2014